all right now let's start talking about the basics of pytorch
자, 이제 pytorch의 기초에 대해 이야기를 시작하겠습니다.
so pytorch is built around tensors
pytorch는 텐서를 중심으로 구축됩니다.
which are really similar to numpy arrays
numpy 배열과 정말 유사합니다.
and basically a lot of the things that we talked about in the previous video with numpy you can do the exact same thing on pytorch tensors too
그리고 기본적으로 이전 비디오에서 numpy로 이야기한 많은 것들이 pytorch 텐서에서도 똑같은 일을 할 수 있습니다.
so for example i can define two pytorch tensors that have the same shape and then i can add them together just like i did with numpy arrays
예를 들어 모양이 같은 두 개의 pytorch 텐서를 정의한 다음 numpy 배열에서 했던 것처럼 함께 추가할 수 있습니다.
I can also do reductions just like I do in numpy and i can specify axes along which i want to do that reduction
또한 numpy에서 하는 것처럼 축소를 수행할 수 있으며 해당 축소를 수행하려는 축을 지정할 수 있습니다.
there's a minor difference which is that in pytorch the argument is called dim for dimension instead of axes but otherwise they're the same
pytorch에서 인수는 axes 대신 dimesion(차원)이라는 의미로 dim이라고 하지만 다른 것은 동일합니다.
and just like numpy pytorch will also try to broadcast operations if possible
numpy pytorch와 마찬가지로 가능한 경우 브로드캐스트 작업도 시도합니다.
so if i have these two tensors of different shapes i can still add them together because they'll be broadcasted
따라서 다른 모양의 이 두 텐서가 있으면 브로드캐스트될 것이기 때문에 여전히 함께 추가할 수 있습니다.
something you'll probably do pretty often is move between numpy arrays and pytorch tensors
아마도 꽤 자주 할 일은 numpy 배열과 pytorch 텐서간의 변환을하는 것입니다.
we'll talk a bit more about why that's necessary a little later
그것이 왜 필요한지에 대해서는 잠시 후에 더 이야기할 것입니다.
but for now let's just show you how that works
하지만 지금은 작동 방식을 보여 드리겠습니다.
so let's say you have this numpy array
이 numpy 배열이 있다고 가정 해 봅시다.
it's two by three and i want to convert this to a pytorch tensor
2 x 3이고 이것을 pytorch 텐서로 변환하고 싶습니다.
so to do that i'll be using the torch.from numpy function
그렇게 하기 위해 저는 torch.from numpy 함수를 사용할 것입니다.
and what that does is it gives me a new pytorch tensor
그리고 그것이 하는 일은 나에게 새로운 pytorch 텐서를 제공한다는 것입니다.
but that tensor actually shares the same memory as the original numpy array
그러나 그 텐서는 실제로 원래 numpy 배열과 동일한 메모리를 공유합니다.
so even though on this new tensor x you can do all sorts of pytorch operations on it now
따라서 이 새로운 텐서 x에서 모든 종류의 pytorch 작업을 지금 수행할 수 있지만
it's actually referring to the same part of memory
그것은 실제로 메모리의 동일한 부분을 참조하고 있습니다
so if you mutate the original numpy array
따라서 원래 numpy 배열을 변경하면
that's also going to affect the pytorch tensor and vice versa
그것은 또한 pytorch 텐서에 영향을 미치고 그 반대의 경우도 마찬가지입니다.
by default numpy arrays are going to be the float 64 type
기본적으로 numpy 배열은 float 64 유형이 됩니다.
so if you look at this dtype property whenever you print out a pytorch tensor
따라서 pytorch 텐서를 출력할 때마다 이 dtype 속성을 보면
you can see what data type it is
어떤 데이터 유형인지 알 수 있습니다
most of the time tensors and py torch are actually float32
대부분의 경우 텐서와 파이 토치는 실제로 float32입니다.
so when you convert from numpy over to pytorch
그래서 numpy에서 pytorch로 변환할 때
you'll probably want to actually cast it as a float32 type
실제로 float32 유형으로 캐스팅하고 싶을 것입니다.
just because you don't really need that extra level of precision
추가 정밀도 수준이 실제로 필요하지 않기 때문에
so the way you do that is you can call dot to and you can specify floats integers or whatever you want
그래서 당신이하는 방법은 점을 호출하고 부동 정수 또는 원하는 것을 지정할 수 있다는 것입니다.
and that's how you'd change it to a different data type
다른 데이터 유형으로 변경하는 방법입니다.
so here since we converted it basically to the default floating point type
여기에서는 기본적으로 기본 부동 소수점 유형으로 변환했기 때문에
you'll see that it doesn't have a d type specified
dtype이 지정되지 않은 것을 볼 수 있습니다.
and finally if you want to go the other way around if you have a pytorch tensor
마지막으로 pytorch 텐서가 있는 경우 다른 방향으로 가고 싶다면
and you want to go back to a numpy array
numpy 배열로 돌아가고 싶을 때는 어떻게 할까요?
you can just call that tensor dot numpy
그 텐서에 점을 찍어 numpy를 호출 할 수 있습니다.
and again this will occupy the same part of memory so mutating one will mutate the other
다시 이것은 메모리의 동일한 부분을 차지하므로 하나를 변경하면 다른 하나가 변경됩니다.
pytorch also has a bunch of built-in functions for neural networks
pytorch에는 신경망용 내장 함수도 많이 있습니다.
and this can be really useful when you're training them
이것은 당신이 그들을 훈련시킬 때 정말 유용할 수 있습니다
you should definitely check out the documentation for a full list of what you can do
당신이 할 수 있는 일의 전체 목록은 문서를 반드시 확인해야 합니다.
chances are whatever you're trying to do there's something in pytorch that already accomplishes it
기회는 당신이하려고하는 것이 무엇이든 pytorch에 이미 그것을 달성하는 무언가가 있습니다.
but just to give you a sense of how much is available to you
하지만 얼마나 많은 것을 사용할 수 있는지에 대한 감각을 제공하기 위해
all sorts of activation functions like relu sigmoid 10h there are functions for each of these
relu sigmoid 10h와 같은 모든 종류의 활성화 함수에는 각각에 대한 함수가 있습니다.
along with whatever numerical optimizations need to be done
수행해야 하는 수치 최적화와 함께
so you don't have to worry about those
그래서 당신은 그것에 대해 걱정할 필요가 없습니다
you can just use the built-in by torch functions
내장 토치 기능을 사용할 수 있습니다.
there's also the softmax function if you're trying to predict probabilities
확률을 예측하려는 경우 softmax 기능도 있습니다.
and you can call softmax on some pytorch tensor specify some dimension along which you're taking those
일부 pytorch 텐서에서 softmax를 호출할 수 있습니다.
I'm taking this off now so dimension equals negative one means i'm using the last dimension so basically each row is going to be a set of probabilities
차원이 음수와 같도록 이제 이것을 벗고 있습니다. 즉, 마지막 차원을 사용하고 있으므로 기본적으로 각 행은 일련의 확률이 될 것입니다.
and then when i call torsion soft max i convert these logics to probabilities
그런 다음 비틀림 소프트 맥스를 호출할 때 이 논리를 확률로 변환합니다.
so probably the most critical part of pytorch is the way that it does automatic differentiation
따라서 아마도 pytorch의 가장 중요한 부분은 자동 미분을 수행하는 방식일 것입니다.
because if you've ever tried to do back prop by hand
왜냐하면 당신이 손으로 역전파를 시도한 적이 있다면
it's really tedious and it's not something that you want to try to implement yourself in code
정말 지루하고 코드에서 구현하려고 하는 것이 아닙니다.
so this is one of the most important parts of what pytorch does for you in terms of training neural networks
이것은 신경망 훈련 측면에서 pytorch가 수행하는 가장 중요한 부분 중 하나입니다.
so let's say we have some loss function and we want to evaluate the gradient of that loss function with respect to the inputs x and y
손실 함수가 있고 입력 x 및 y에 대한 손실 함수의 기울기를 평가하려고 한다고 가정해 보겠습니다.
so the way you do that is when you define the tensor you can additionally specify requires valuables true
따라서 추가로 지정할 수 있는 텐서를 정의할 때 값이 필요합니다. true
and that will basically tell pytorch that it should keep track of the gradients for this variable
그리고 그것은 기본적으로 pytorch에게 이 변수에 대한 그라디언트를 추적해야 한다고 알려줍니다.
by default if you don't specify that it's just going to be a fixed tensor and there's going to be no gradient tracked for back prop
기본적으로 고정 텐서가 되도록 지정하지 않고 back prop에 대해 추적되는 그래디언트가 없는 경우
so what happens when you specify requires grad equals true is the tensor will keep track of two pieces of information
따라서 require grad equals true를 지정하면 텐서가 두 가지 정보를 추적하게 됩니다.
the first is the data which is just the original values in the tensor
첫 번째는 텐서의 원래 값인 데이터입니다.
but also have a dot grad property which stores the gradient
그러나 그라디언트를 저장하는 dot grad 속성도 있습니다.
right now you'll notice that dog grad is none just because you haven't really done any computation with x yet
지금 당장 당신은 x로 어떤 계산도 하지 않았기 때문에 dog grad가 없음을 알 수 있을 것입니다.
you haven't told pytorch what to take the gradients of
당신은 pytorch에게 그라디언트를 취할 것을 말하지 않았습니다.
so there's nothing inside the x.grad property
x.grad 속성 안에는 아무것도 없습니다.
but let's see what happens when we define a loss
하지만 손실을 정의할 때 어떤 일이 발생하는지 봅시다.
so here we're doing some calculations that involve x and y
여기에서 x와 y를 포함하는 몇 가지 계산을 하고 있습니다.
we're summing them together to get a scalar loss
우리는 그것들을 합산하여 스칼라 손실을 얻습니다.
and that resulting tensor loss you'll notice has this grad function property
그 결과 텐서 손실에는 이 grad 함수 속성이 있습니다.
and the reason for that is basically anytime you do any kind of operations on pytorch tensors that have requires grad equals true
그 이유는 기본적으로 grad가 true여야 하는 pytorch 텐서에서 모든 종류의 작업을 수행할 때마다입니다.
pytorch will implicitly build out its own graph of all the computations you're doing
pytorch는 여러분이 수행하는 모든 계산에 대한 자체 그래프를 암시적으로 구축합니다.
and for each tensor it keeps track of which function was applied before it to get to that tensor
각 텐서에 대해 해당 텐서에 도달하기 전에 어떤 함수가 적용되었는지 추적합니다.
so this example grad function is going to be sum backward zero
따라서 이 예제 grad 함수는 뒤로 0으로 합산됩니다.
because the way that you got to the loss was that you called dot sum on something before it
왜냐하면 당신이 손실에 도달한 방법은 당신이 그 전에 무언가에 대해 도트합을 호출했기 때문입니다.
so the cool thing is we can actually trace our way back through these grad functions
멋진 점은 실제로 이러한 grad 함수를 통해 다시 추적할 수 있다는 것입니다.
all the way to the beginning to see the computation graph that pytorch has in its internal representation
pytorch가 내부 표현에 가지고 있는 계산 그래프를 보기 위해 처음부터 끝까지
so this is the computation graph of that loss function we calculated earlier
이것은 우리가 이전에 계산한 손실 함수의 계산 그래프입니다.
and we're printing this from loss going backwards so the first thing is sum backward
그리고 우리는 이것을 뒤로가는 손실에서 인쇄하므로 첫 번째 것은 뒤로 합입니다.
and if we take that grad function and figure out what came before it it's saying that the sum came from this thing before it which came from pow backward zero
그리고 만약 우리가 그 grad 함수를 취해서 그 합이 pow backward zero에서 나온 것보다 앞의 것에서 왔다는 것을 의미하기 전에 무엇이 왔는지 알아낸다면
because we squared something to get to it
우리는 그것을 얻기 위해 무언가를 제곱했기 때문에
tracing one step backwards we have add
한 단계 뒤로 추적 추가
and then tracing one step backwards
그런 다음 한 단계 뒤로 추적
you'll notice that we have two different things
당신은 우리가 두 가지 다른 것을 가지고 있음을 알 수 있습니다
because the addition operation the result of the addition came from two variables
덧셈 연산의 덧셈 결과가 두 변수에서 나왔기 때문에
the first was some tensor y for which we said requires grad equals true
첫 번째는 grad가 true여야 한다고 말한 일부 텐서 y였습니다.
so that's why we have this accumulate grad operation
그래서 우리는 이 누적 대학원 작업을 가지고 있습니다.
another thing was some sort of multiplication operation so we have a mole backward
또 다른 것은 일종의 곱셈 연산이었습니다.
and then if we go back one more step
그리고 다시 한 발짝 뒤로 물러나면
we see these other two inputs
우리는 이 다른 두 입력을 봅니다
we have x where we specified requires grad equals true
우리는 grad가 true와 같아야 한다고 지정한 곳에 x가 있습니다.
and then we have this other value two which is basically not something that's storing gradient
기본적으로 그라디언트를 저장하는 것이 아닌 다른 값 2가 있습니다.
so that doesn't have its own grad function
자체 grad 기능이 없기 때문에
so each of the yellow nodes above in this computation graph has a dot grad property
따라서 이 계산 그래프에서 위의 각 노란색 노드에는 도트 그라드 속성이 있습니다.
and when you do back prop
그리고 당신이 다시 소품을 할 때
and pytorch that direct property is going to be storing the gradients with respect to the loss
그리고 직접 속성이 손실에 대한 그라디언트를 저장할 것이라는 pytorch
so to perform backprop we are going to choose some scalar at some point in the computation graph
따라서 역전파를 수행하기 위해 계산 그래프의 특정 지점에서 일부 스칼라를 선택할 것입니다.
so here we'll choose loss
그래서 여기서 우리는 손실을 선택할 것입니다
and we'll call lost.backward
그리고 우리는 lost.backward를 호출할 것입니다
and once that's done all of these yellow nodes will have their gradients populated
완료되면 이 모든 노란색 노드에 그라디언트가 채워집니다.
and if you print out the dot grad properties you can see that these now have values
dot grad 속성을 출력하면 이제 값이 있음을 알 수 있습니다.
so something that's a bit strange in pytorch is that the gradients actually accumulate
pytorch에서 약간 이상한 점은 그래디언트가 실제로 누적된다는 것입니다.
so if you do the same operation again and then you call last backward again
따라서 동일한 작업을 다시 수행한 다음 마지막으로 다시 뒤로 호출하면
it won't like overwrite the previous dot grad it'll actually add to it
이전 도트 그레이드를 덮어쓰는 것을 좋아하지 않으며 실제로 추가됩니다.
so you'll end up getting twice the gradient
그래서 당신은 두 배의 그라디언트를 얻게 될 것입니다
and the reason this might sometimes be useful is for example
이것이 때때로 유용할 수 있는 이유는 예를 들어
if you have multiple loss functions
여러 손실 함수가 있는 경우
and you want to take the gradient with respect to both of those
그리고 당신은 그 두 가지 모두에 대해 그라디언트를 취하고 싶습니다.
even if they don't use the same parameters or anything like that
동일한 매개변수 또는 이와 유사한 것을 사용하지 않더라도
you can still do these operations and call dot backward
여전히 이러한 작업을 수행하고 dot를 뒤로 호출할 수 있습니다.
so in this case i have some loss function that only depends on x
그래서 이 경우 x에만 의존하는 손실 함수가 있습니다.
and when i call that backwards it's going to keep the previous ones which came from the other loss function
그리고 그것을 거꾸로 호출하면 다른 손실 함수에서 가져온 이전 항목을 유지할 것입니다.
but also you'll notice that x dot grad changed here because of this second loss function
그러나 이 두 번째 손실 함수 때문에 x dot grad가 여기에서 변경되었음을 알 수 있습니다.
so that can be useful sometimes if you're working with more complicated architectures that involve multiple loss functions or things like that
따라서 여러 손실 함수 또는 이와 유사한 것을 포함하는 더 복잡한 아키텍처로 작업하는 경우 유용할 수 있습니다.
for the most part though pretty much what you need to know is you define these operations
대부분의 경우 알아야 할 사항은 이러한 작업을 정의한다는 것입니다.
so you define this loss function here and then you just say lost backward and your gradients will get populated for you
여기에서 이 손실 함수를 정의한 다음 뒤로 손실되었다고 말하면 그라디언트가 자동으로 채워집니다.
something that you will probably do pretty often is stopping and starting gradients
당신이 아마 꽤 자주 할 일은 그라디언트를 멈추고 시작하는 것입니다
so if you don't specify requires right equals true then by default that tensor will not have any gradient tracked
따라서 require right equals true를 지정하지 않으면 기본적으로 텐서는 추적되는 그라디언트가 없습니다.
so here x will have its gradient tracked but y won't
여기서 x는 그래디언트를 추적하지만 y는 추적하지 않습니다.
so if I compute the loss and do last step backwards you'll notice that x dot gradle is populated but y dot grad wasn't
따라서 손실을 계산하고 마지막 단계를 거꾸로 수행하면 x dot gradle이 채워지지만 y dot grad는 채워지지 않았음을 알 수 있습니다.
you can always change your mind afterwards after initializing the tensor
텐서를 초기화한 후에는 언제든지 마음을 바꿀 수 있습니다.
you can change requires grad to be true
당신은 변경할 수 있습니다 grad는 사실이 필요합니다
and then as long as it's true at the point where you call
그리고 당신이 전화한 시점에서 그것이 사실인 한
where you compute the loss and do law stuff backward
손실을 계산하고 법률 작업을 거꾸로 수행하는 곳
then you're going to get a gradient
그러면 그라디언트가 생깁니다.
but you have to make sure to do this before you actually do any computations
그러나 실제로 계산을 수행하기 전에 이 작업을 수행해야 합니다.
because remember pytorch needs to be able to store the grad functions for each of these to remember where they came from
pytorch는 각각의 grad 함수를 저장할 수 있어야 어디서 왔는지 기억할 수 있기 때문입니다.
you can also cut a gradient by calling y dot detach so let's say you have these two variables where you do want to track the gradient normally
y.detach를 호출하여 그라디언트를 잘라낼 수도 있습니다. 일반적으로 그라디언트를 추적하려는 이 두 변수가 있다고 가정해 보겠습니다.
but for some reason later on you want to do a calculation that doesn't uh have its gradient tracked
하지만 나중에 어떤 이유로 인해 그라디언트를 추적하지 않는 계산을 하고 싶습니다.
so an example this might be if x and y are like the weights of a neural network
예를 들어 x와 y가 신경망의 가중치와 같다면
when you do training you definitely want requires grad equals true
훈련을 할 때 grad는 true와 같아야 합니다.
but when it's time to actually evaluate you might not want to have any gradient on it
그러나 실제로 평가할 때 그라디언트를 원하지 않을 수 있습니다.
so you can call why not detach and that's not in place operation it's going to return an entirely new tensor that doesn't have requires grad equals true
따라서 분리하지 않는 이유를 호출할 수 있으며 작업이 수행되지 않는 완전히 새로운 텐서를 반환할 것입니다. grad는 true가 필요합니다.
so the original y is actually still staying the same
따라서 원래 y는 실제로 여전히 동일하게 유지됩니다.
but now if you call that step backward
하지만 지금 당신이 그 단계를 뒤로 부르면
you notice that y detached doesn't have its grad populated
y detached에는 grad가 채워져 있지 않습니다.
so a few things to watch out for
그래서 주의해야 할 몇 가지
and then we'll talk about like when exactly you'll use these things
그런 다음 정확히 언제 이러한 것들을 사용할 것인지에 대해 이야기할 것입니다.
so the first is you can't do any in place operations if the tensor has requires grad equals true so here for y
따라서 첫 번째는 텐서가 grad가 true와 같아야 하는 경우 제자리 작업을 수행할 수 없다는 것입니다.
I can't mutate y by like calling y dot add underscore or like modifying a single element of y
y dot add underscore를 호출하거나 y의 단일 요소를 수정하는 것과 같이 y를 변경할 수 없습니다.
if I try to do that i'll get an error message
그렇게하려고하면 오류 메시지가 나타납니다.
I'm mutating y and then here it'll give me an error
나는 y를 변경하고 있으며 여기에 오류가 발생합니다.
and the reason is because pytorch is only able to keep track of your operations for backdrop purposes
그 이유는 pytorch가 배경 목적으로만 작업을 추적할 수 있기 때문입니다.
if you write them in terms of these pure functions like adding things multiplying things
그것들을 곱하는 것을 더하는 것과 같은 이러한 순수한 기능의 관점에서 작성한다면
you can't go in and directly modify a tensor or else
텐서를 직접 수정할 수 없습니다.
pytorch won't realize that something changed and your back prop is gonna get messed up
pytorch는 무언가가 변경되어 역전파가 엉망이 될 것이라는 사실을 깨닫지 못합니다.
and for pretty much the same reason you also can't uh convert a tensor that still has requires quite equals true to numpy
그리고 거의 같은 이유로 여전히 numpy에 대해 상당히 동일한 것을 요구하는 텐서를 변환할 수 없습니다.
because remember they share the same memory so we don't want to accidentally modify the numpy array and mess with the back prop process for this tensor
왜냐하면 우리는 실수로 numpy 배열을 수정하고 이 텐서에 대한 back prop 프로세스를 엉망으로 만들고 싶지 않기 때문에 동일한 메모리를 공유한다는 것을 기억하기 때문입니다.
so instead if you actually want to convert that tensor to numpy
대신 실제로 해당 텐서를 numpy로 변환하려는 경우
you want to detach it first so we have the tensor y you can call y dot detach dot numpy
먼저 분리하기를 원하므로 텐서 y가 있습니다. y dot detach dot numpy라고 부를 수 있습니다.
there's a weird gotcha here which is that even though y dot detach returns a new tensor that doesn't require grad
y dot detach가 grad를 필요로 하지 않는 새 텐서를 반환하더라도 이상한 문제가 있습니다.
that tensor still occupies the same memory as y
텐서는 여전히 y와 같은 메모리를 차지합니다.
and unfortunately you can still accidentally like you can make changes to this y dot detach or y not detach that numpy
불행히도 여전히 실수로 이 y dot detach를 변경하거나 해당 numpy를 분리하지 않을 수 있습니다.
and that will end up affecting y as well which will mess up your gradients
그러면 y에도 영향을 미치게 되어 그라디언트가 엉망이 됩니다.
so if you wanted to convert a pytorch tensor that has requires grad equals true to either a numpy array or a tensor without gradient
따라서 grad가 필요한 pytorch 텐서를 numpy 배열이나 그라디언트가 없는 텐서로 true로 변환하려는 경우
and you want to be able to safely mutate it
그리고 당신은 그것을 안전하게 돌연변이시킬 수 있기를 원합니다
what you have to do is not only detach it but also called dot clone which will give you an actual copy of the tensor in new memory
당신이해야 할 일은 그것을 분리 할뿐만 아니라 새로운 메모리에 텐서의 실제 사본을 제공하는 점 복제라고도합니다.
so this is all kind of abstract right now you might be wondering like why you need all these things
그래서 이것은 지금 모든 종류의 추상적 인 것입니다. 왜 이 모든 것이 필요한지 궁금해 할 것입니다.
converting to and from numpy detaching requirement and things like that
numpy 분리 요구 사항 및 이와 유사한 것으로 변환
and at least as it relates to rl
그리고 적어도 rl과 관련하여
usually what ends up happening is that
일반적으로 결국 일어나는 일은
sometimes you're working with numpy arrays and sometimes you're working with tensors
때로는 numpy 배열로 작업하고 때로는 텐서로 작업합니다.
so as an example let's say you have some kind of environment where you want to train your agent in
예를 들어 에이전트를 교육하려는 환경이 있다고 가정해 보겠습니다.
and then you have a model which is represented by like a series of pytorch tensors
그런 다음 일련의 pytorch 텐서처럼 표현되는 모델이 있습니다.
usually your simulator for the environment is going to be working with numpy arrays not pie torch tensors
일반적으로 환경에 대한 시뮬레이터는 파이 토치 텐서가 아닌 numpy 배열로 작업할 것입니다.
just because uh it's probably a good idea to keep the simulator code kind of separate
시뮬레이터 코드를 별도의 유형으로 유지하는 것이 좋습니다.
it shouldn't depend on what deep learning framework you're using to train your agent
에이전트를 훈련시키는 데 사용하는 딥 러닝 프레임워크에 의존해서는 안 됩니다.
so that's the meter is going to be working with numpy arrays
그래서 그것은 미터가 numpy 배열과 함께 작동할 것입니다.
and if you have like a data set full of like states represented as numpy arrays from this simulated environment
이 시뮬레이션된 환경에서 numpy 배열로 표시되는 유사한 상태로 가득 찬 데이터 세트가 있는 경우
and you want to start doing training for rl
rl에 대한 학습을 시작하고 싶을 것이다.
what you'll do is you'll convert from those numpy arrays to pytorch tensors
당신이 할 일은 그 numpy 배열에서 pytorch 텐서로 변환하는 것입니다
and using those pi towards tensors you can do training on your model
그리고 그 파이를 텐서에 사용하면 모델에 대한 훈련을 할 수 있습니다.
and then when it's time to actually make predictions
그리고 실제로 예측을 할 때
you'll get some kind of state from the environment which is a numpy array
numpy 배열인 환경에서 일종의 상태를 얻을 수 있습니다.
so you'll want to convert that to a pytorch tensor
그래서 당신은 그것을 pytorch 텐서로 변환하고 싶을 것입니다
use that tensor run it through your model and get some predicted action maybe
해당 텐서를 사용하여 모델을 실행하고 예측된 조치를 취하십시오.
but you'll probably want to detach that action and convert it back to an numpy array
그러나 아마도 해당 작업을 분리하고 다시 numpy 배열로 변환하고 싶을 것입니다.
that's just usually a nice convention
그것은 단지 일반적으로 좋은 컨벤션입니다
just because the output of your policy is not really something that you need to track the gradient for or that you need to do any further pytorch operations on
정책의 출력이 실제로 그라디언트를 추적해야 하거나 추가 pytorch 작업을 수행해야 하는 것이 아니기 때문에
so it's a good idea to only use pytorch for that middle layer where you're doing like anything related to training or inference
따라서 훈련 또는 추론과 관련된 작업을 수행하는 중간 계층에만 pytorch를 사용하는 것이 좋습니다.
but then use numpy arrays to actually represent the states of your environment
하지만 numpy 배열을 사용하여 실제로 환경의 상태를 나타냅니다.
and the actions that you choose to take
그리고 당신이 취하기로 선택한 행동
so that's an example of when you would need to work with these conversion functions or use things like detach
이것은 이러한 변환 함수로 작업하거나 분리와 같은 것을 사용해야 하는 경우의 예입니다.